http://www.addonheadrest.com/privacy.html

Add On HeadRestWhiplash Protection - Comfort & SupportEffective Neck & Back Pain ReliefHelps Reduce Driving Tension & FatigueImproved Whiplash Injury ProtectionPhysician Approved
Add On HeadRest Privacy Policy
Add On HeadRest
Add On HeadRest FeaturesWhiplash Injury ProtectionPhysician RecommendedCrash Test ResultsWhiplash AccidentsNeck PainBack PainCar Head RestraintsTestimonialsAdd On Headrest FAQOrder Add On Headrest
Your privacy ...
At Posture Med, LLC we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you only to process orders. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
What information do we collect? How do we use it?
When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address and shipping address. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.
How do you process orders?
We use Paypal as our merchant, they process all orders for Posture Med, LLC. We assure you that Paypal uses the latest technology to ensure the most secure ordering online. Posture Med, LLC will never have access to your credit card information nor will we ask for it. You do not need a paypal account to place your order.
How does Posture Med, LLC protect customer information?
When you place orders we provide a secure server via Paypal. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data collected is protected against unauthorized access.
What about "cookies"?
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, they only provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, and traffic patterns.
Will Posture Med, LLC disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Posture Med, LLC may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of sale or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of our users, or others.
In summary
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at addonheadrest.com possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
Your consent
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Posture Med, LLC. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
About Us | Privacy Policy | Contact AddOnHeadrest | Neck Pain Relief | Disclaimer
